<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog</title>
    <link>https://hitvoice.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>runqiyang@gmail.com (Runqi Yang)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>runqiyang@gmail.com (Runqi Yang)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hitvoice.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://hitvoice.github.io/post/nn-basic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>runqiyang@gmail.com (Runqi Yang)</author>
      <guid>https://hitvoice.github.io/post/nn-basic/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheatsheet for Python Data Analysis</title>
      <link>https://hitvoice.github.io/post/python/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>runqiyang@gmail.com (Runqi Yang)</author>
      <guid>https://hitvoice.github.io/post/python/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s not just another cheatsheet. Here are most frequent and important methods in a machine learning project with CAUTIONS and TIPS. Some other useful tools, like bcolz and Jupyter notebook widgets, are also covered.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learing</title>
      <link>https://hitvoice.github.io/post/dmnotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>runqiyang@gmail.com (Runqi Yang)</author>
      <guid>https://hitvoice.github.io/post/dmnotes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This post aims to share a list of notes (compiled by myself) on some important machine learning topics. Most of the concepts are mathematical, but after all, math is the most precise language!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hitvoice.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>runqiyang@gmail.com (Runqi Yang)</author>
      <guid>https://hitvoice.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Runqi Yang (杨润琦)  NLP Engineer  in Alime X Lab Alibaba Group  hitvoice
 runqiyang@gmail.com
  Biography I&#39;m a NLP engineer @Alibaba. I received my M.Sc. degree in Computer Science in 2019 and B.Sc. degree in Electronic Engineering in 2016, both from Nanjing University.
Publications  (ACL19) Simple and Effective Text Matching with Richer Alignment Features (1st author, pdf | github) (AAAI18) Multi-Entity Aspect-Based Sentiment Analysis with Context, Entity and Aspect Memory (2nd author, link | pdf | code and data)  Contributions to Open Source Projects  my repository, implementation of DrQA (300+ stars, on DWANBench leaderboard) pytorch/pytorch: bug reporting #1687 #3789 pytorch/fairseq: pull request #134 facebookresearch/ParlAI: pull request #176 AIChallenger/AI_Challenger: pull request #16#19#25 my GithubGist  Articles and Talks  2018, Introduction to Text Generation (slides) 2017, interview with Zhihu machine learning team, Machine Learning Theory and Practice (in Chinese) (link) 2017, Introduction to Machine Reading Comprehension (slides) 2017, interview with iFLYTEK Research, Attention-over-Attention: A Way Towards Machine Reading Comprehension (in Chinese) (link) 2016, Pracical Advice on Machine Learning Projects (slides)  Awards and Honors  2017, The Outstanding Camper Award at DeeCamp, Sinovation Ventures 2013, Outstanding Student of Nanjing University  Miscellaneous  My name pronounces as &amp;quot;Ren-Chee&amp;quot; (sounding like &amp;quot;rent&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;cheese&amp;quot; without &amp;quot;t&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;se&amp;quot;) I love guitar, musical, drama and paiting.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>